omgwut.xyz 2016-06-02

# TOS & Privacy Policy | OMGWUT?

## Contents:

  1. [Terms of Service](http://omgwut.xyz/tos-privacy-policy/#atospp-terms)
  2. [Privacy Policy](http://omgwut.xyz/tos-privacy-policy/#atospp-privacy)

## Terms of Service:

The following terms and conditions govern all use of the OMGWUT.com website and all content, services and products available at or through the website (taken together, the Website). The Website is owned and operated by OMGWUT?, LLC (“OMGWUT?”). The Website is offered subject to your acceptance without modification of all of the terms and conditions contained herein and all other operating rules, policies (including, without limitation, OMGWUT’s Privacy Policy) and procedures that may be published from time to time on this Site by OMGWUT? (collectively, the “Agreement”).

Please read this Agreement carefully before accessing or using the Website. By accessing or using any part of the web site, you agree to become bound by the terms and conditions of this agreement. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this agreement, then you may not access the Website or use any services. If these terms and conditions are considered an offer by OMGWUT?, acceptance is expressly limited to these terms. The Website is available only to individuals who are at least 13 years old.

## Privacy Policy:

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, OMGWUT? collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. OMGWUT’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how OMGWUT’s visitors use its website. From time to time, OMGWUT? may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

OMGWUT? also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on OMGWUT.com blogs/sites. OMGWUT? only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

### Aggregated Statistics

OMGWUT? may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. OMGWUT? may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, OMGWUT? does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

OMGWUT? discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on OMGWUT’s behalf or to provide services available at OMGWUT’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using OMGWUT’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. OMGWUT? will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, OMGWUT? discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when OMGWUT? believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of OMGWUT?, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an OMGWUT? website and have supplied your email address, OMGWUT? may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with OMGWUT? and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. OMGWUT? takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. OMGWUT? uses cookies to help OMGWUT? identify and track visitors, their usage of OMGWUT? website, and their website access preferences. OMGWUT? visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using OMGWUT’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of OMGWUT’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

### Business Transfers

If OMGWUT?, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that OMGWUT? goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of OMGWUT? may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by OMGWUT? and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, OMGWUT? may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in OMGWUT’s sole discretion. OMGWUT? encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a OMGWUT.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
